Raymond has a question to do with the use of non-US alphabet characters.
Raymond 有个问题 处理使用非美国字母字符的问题
When he first wrote programs with text in Spanish and ran them using Python,
当他第一次以西班牙文写程序时 使用了文字 并使用 Python 来执行
he got an error--syntax error "non-ASCII character."
他得到了一个 error —— 语法错误 "非 ASCII 字符"
He did not get that error when running the same code in IDLE. It worked as it should.
在 IDE 执行相同的代码 并不会得到这个错误它运作正常
He solved this by changing the encoding.
他更改编码 (encoding) 以解决这个问题
So as we're building a search engine that will scan pages in different languages
所以 当我们创建搜索引擎时 它会扫描不同语言的页面
and perhaps use different language interfaces, how should we change our code
可能使用了不同的语言页面 我们应如何改变我们的代码
so that it does not run into problems with encoding? What should our default character set be?
这样 它就不会有编码的问题？我们预设的字符集应该是什么？
Thanks for the question, Raymond. This is a really good point to bring up.
谢谢你的问题 Raymond 谈到这个观点真的很好
As you take inputs that include more languages than just English
当你采取的输入 包括了多个语言 不仅是英语时
the character sets are different.
字符集是不同的
If you look at a webpage, there's a header in the webpage
如果你看一个网页 网页有一个标题
that identifies what characters set it's using.
标题识别了它使用的字符集
This is part of the HTTP protocol to have a header that describes the content type,
这是 HTTP 协定的一部分 要有标题 描述内容的类型
which includes the character set.
包含字符集
The character set can be selected from a few different ones.
字符集可以从一些不同的字符集中选择
The most common one is called UTF-8.
最普遍的一种称为 UTF-8
That's using a way of encoding characters that makes the simple characters
它使用编码字符的方式 可以使简单的字符
that can be encoded in just 7 bits.
以仅仅 7 个比特 (bit) 来编码
This is the character set that is known as ASCII.
这被称为 ASCII 字符集
These are characters that are common in English.
这些都是在英文中常见的字符
It doesn't cover all the characters that are used in all other languages,
它不包括在其他语言中 使用的所有字符
but those 7-bit characters can be encoded using a small amount of space.
但是 这些 7 比特的字符 能以少量的空间进行编码
The standard we've been using in Python with standard strings is that they're all ASCII.
在 Python 里的标准字符串 其使用的标准都是 ASCII
Each character is 1 byte.
每个字符是一个位元组 (byte)
There's only 255 possible characters that can be encoded in 1 byte though.
仅有 255 个可能的字符 可以在 1 个位元组 (byte) 做编码
If you're wanting to deal with more languages, you need to use different characters.
如果你想要处理更多的语言 你需要使用不同的字符
The way to do that is called Unicode.
要做到这一点的方法称为 Unicode
Unicode is a character set that can support large numbers of characters.
Unicode 是一种字符集 可以支持大量的字符
It's actually a way of encoding characters that doesn't have a limit on
它实际上是一种编码字符的方法
how many characters you can support.
没有限制你可以支持多少字符
A way of encoding those that makes it efficient when the characters are small
有一种编码方式 当字符少时 其效率高
but allows you to still encode a large number of characters is called UTF-8,
但仍允许你编码数量大的字符 称为 UTF-8
which is what most web browsers use.
这为大多数 web 浏览器所使用
To deal with this in Python, what you'd have to deal with instead of standard strings is Unicode strings.
为了在 Python 处理这个问题 你必须使用 Unicode 字符串 而不是标准字符串
There is a built-in type for Unicode characters.
有一个内置类型的 Unicode 字符
You can convert a string to Unicode by using Unicode.
你可以透过使用 Unicode 将字符串转换为 Unicode
Then there are ways of encoding Unicode in other character sets.
然后有其他字符集 有方法来编码 Unicode
If you wanted to build a web search engine that can deal with text that's not using
如果你想要建立一个搜索引擎 可以处理文字中 没有使用标准的英文字符集
the standard English character set, you definitely need to worry about handling Unicode
你一定要小心处理 Unicode
and all these different character encodings.
和所有这些不同的字符编码